Guide to the Mary Harron Papers MSS.608
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series V. Unrealized Projects, 1951-2005; 5.08 Linear Feet in 8 manuscript boxes and 2 cassette boxes; 26 audiocassettes; 5 Betacam; 1.28 Megabytes in 30 computer files
  - "I'll Be Your Mirror: Stories of Women in Rock"
    - Interviews and Research
      - Mary Wells -- Research Material, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - Helen Wheels -- Audio Recording, undated (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0085)
      - Vicky Wickham, August 1, 1982
        - Audio Recording -- Tape 1 -- NYC (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0087)
        - Audio Recording -- Tape 2 -- NYC (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0072)
      - Women in Country Music
        - Audio Recording -- Buzz Cason and Billy Smith -- Nashville, November 7, 1983 (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0119)
        - Audio Recording -- Robert K. Oermann, October 18, 1983 (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0114)
        - Research Material, 1979-1982 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - "The Lottery" -- Scene List and Script, undated (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - "Love Affair"
    - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Notes, Outline, and Synopsis, circa 1987 (Box 23, Folder 15-16)
    - Research Material, 1951-1974 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Script by Elizabeth LeCompte and Mary Harron
      - Early Draft and Notes, 1987-1988 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Final First Draft, February 1988 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Second Draft, August 1988 (Box 24, Folder 4-5)
      - Third Draft, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Fifth Draft, August 1990 (Box 24, Folder 7-8)
      - Sixth Draft, September 1990 (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Eighth Draft, December 1990 (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - Tenth Draft, November 1995 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Luna Score Bits/Rentals, undated (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0113)
  - "O" -- Based on the The Story of O
    - Correspondence, Script, and Schedule, 1994-1996 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Proposal and Synopsis, 1995; FA_MSS_608_ER_52
  - Pavement Video -- Treatment, 1997; FA_MSS_608_ER_53
  - "Pipe Dream" -- Script, 1997; FA_MSS_608_ER_44
  - "Please Kill Me"
    - Correspondence and Notes, 1998-2005 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Script by Legs McNeil and Gillian McCain -- First and Second Drafts, 1998-1999 (Box 25, Folder 3-4)
    - Script with Notes (Possibly by Harron), 2002 (Box 25, Folder 5-6)
  - Gerard Sekoto Film -- Proposal from Dictum Publishing, Correspondence, and Background Information, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - "Simply Halston" -- Consulting Contract, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - "Sunday in New York" -- Story Typescript, undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - "Super 8" or "Trouble for Men" -- Scene List, undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - "True Love"
    - Background Information and Court Documents, 1994-1999 (Box 25, Folder 11-12, Box 26, Folder 1-2)
    - Correspondence, Meeting Notes, and Chronologies, 2001-2002 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Scene Outlines and Scripts by Daniel Voll and Cecilia Peck, 2000-2002 (Box 26, Folder 4-6)
  - Unidentified Audio Recording, undated (Box 30, Audiocassette 608.0061)
  - Unidentified Manuscript, undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Unidentified Script Notes, 1997; FA_MSS_608_ER_54
  - Unidentified Treatment by Harron -- Audio Recording, May 17, 1996 (Box 30, Audiocassette 608.0065)
  - Video Recordings -- Brooklyn -- Unidentified Film, undated
    - Coney Island #1 -- Lea's Song, West Side Highway, Wide Shots (Box 36, Betacam 608.003)
    - Coney Island #6 -- Exteriors, Freak Show, Ocean View, Ferris Wheel (Box 35, Betacam 608.0046)
    - Greenpoint #1 -- Block Party, Ana Rosa and Friends, Docks, Ana Rosa's Party (Box 36, Betacam 608.0029)
    - Greenpoint #2 (Box 35, Betacam 608.0176)
    - Greenpoint #3 -- Grown Ups Dance, Birthday Cake (Box 36, Betacam 608.0031)
  - "The Women" -- Myth Synopsis and Recording Transcripts, 1989-1991 (Box 26, Folder 8-9)